[
    { "id": 1, "type": "radio", "question": "1) Which country first colonized India?", "options": ["Portugal", "Dutch", "Britain", "France"], "correct": 0 },
    { "id": 2, "type": "checkbox", "question": "2) What are the official languages of India?", "options": ["Tamil", "Hindi", "Telugu", "English"], "correct": [1, 3] },
    { "id": 3, "type": "dropdown", "question": "3) What is the capital of Portugal?", "options": ["London", "Barcelona", "Lisbon", "Madrid"], "correct": 2 },
    { "id": 4, "type": "text", "question": "4) What is the largest mammal?", "correct": "Blue Whale" },
    { "id": 5, "type": "radio", "question": "5) How many sides are in Nanogon?", "options": ["7", "8", "9", "10"], "correct": 2 },
    { "id": 6, "type": "checkbox", "question": "6) What are the functions of OS?", "options": ["Memory management", "Storage management", "Resource management", "None of the above"], "correct": [0, 1, 2] },
    { "id": 7, "type": "dropdown", "question": "7) What is the second stage of Data Science Process?", "options": ["Goal Setting", "Data Mining", "Building a Model", "Data Acquisition"], "correct": 3 },
    { "id": 8, "type": "text", "question": "8) Who invented the Turing machine?", "correct": "Alan Turing" },
    { "id": 9, "type": "radio", "question": "9) What is the oldest software development model?", "options": ["Waterfall model", "Agile model", "Rapid Application model", "V shape model"], "correct": 0 },
    { "id": 10, "type": "checkbox", "question": "10) What are the non-linear data structures?", "options": ["Graph", "Stack", "Queue", "Tree"], "correct": [0, 3] },
    { "id": 11, "type": "dropdown", "question": "11) Which company developed Elden Ring?", "options": ["Santa Monica Studios", "Rockstar Games", "From Software", "Ubisoft"], "correct": 2 },
    { "id": 12, "type": "text", "question": "12) Who is the protagonist of God of War?", "correct": "Kratos" },
    { "id": 13, "type": "radio", "question": "13) How many protagonists are in GTA V?", "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "correct": 1 },
    { "id": 14, "type": "checkbox", "question": "14) Who are the main characters in The Last Of Us?", "options": ["Tommy", "Rebecca", "Joel", "Ellie"], "correct": [2, 3] },
    { "id": 15, "type": "dropdown", "question": "15) In which game did Lady Dimitrescu appear?", "options": ["Resident Evil", "Bloodborne", "Dark Souls", "Devil May Cry"], "correct": 0 },
    { "id": 16, "type": "text", "question": "16) Who is the protagonist of Attack On Titan?", "correct": "Eren Yeager" },
    { "id": 17, "type": "radio", "question": "17) What is the real name of L in Death Note?", "options": ["Lelouch", "Levi", "Lawliet", "Laufey"], "correct": 2 },
    { "id": 18, "type": "checkbox", "question": "18) Who are the arch enemies?", "options": ["Gojo", "Yuji", "Mahito", "Nanami"], "correct": [1, 3] },
    { "id": 19, "type": "dropdown", "question": "19) Who is the strongest character in One Punch Man?", "options": ["Genos", "Boros", "Blast", "Saitama"], "correct": 3 },
    { "id": 20, "type": "text", "question": "20) What is the last name of Edward in Fullmetal Alchemist?", "correct": "Elric" }
]
